Preliminary guide to the Robert Sargent literary papers, 1923-2006 MS2308
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Poetry, 1961-2006; Series 3
  - Poems and other writings, undated; Series 3 Subseries 1
    - Laura, on Judy, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - The Learners, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Leave it to the Hands, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Lending "The King of the Golden River", Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - A Letter to Cecelia, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Letter for my Daughter, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Lincoln Only Used One That, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - A Limerick for Lula, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - The Lineman, Remembering, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - The Literary Critic, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - The Literate Pianist, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Logan's Speech, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - The Logician, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Lone Hawk, Comanche County, 1700, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Looking for Oldness, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - The Long Search, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Lord of the Leaves, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Lord Nelson, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Lost and Found, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Lost Knowledge, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - The Lost Poems (Retitled), Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Lula and I, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Lula and the Mirror, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Lula and Trevor, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Lula's Call, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Lula Comforts Daddy, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Lula's Choice, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Lula's Friends, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Lunch, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - The Lyricist, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Making History, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Mary at Galilee, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Matisse, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Mature Critic, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Maturity, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Maybe, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - May Miller, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - The Meaning Exactly, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Madea At The Kitchen Sink, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Medusa, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Memory, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - A Message to Dr. Johnson, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - The Message, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Milestones, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Mildred Bailey, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Mimi at a Restaurant, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Miracles, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Miss Birdie, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Mississippi Jukejoint, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Mister Lester January, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - A Morning Happening, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Mrs. Siddons, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Monet's "Poplars on the Eptte" 1891, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Monody for Bowie, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - The Moon and The Convey, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Mother, Not Man, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Mount McKinley, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Moring, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Mowing the Lawn, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Mr Bud in Action, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Mr Buddy Bishop of Salem, VA, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Mr. Geoffrey Smith, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Mr Gray, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Mr Mencken, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Mr Santayana, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Mundane Questions, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - My Father & Huey Long, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - My Father and Russia, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - My Father: New-Orleans, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - My Friend Cavalieri, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - My Friend Cavalieri (II), Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - My Friend Chilton, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - My Grandson Billy, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - My Lovely One She, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - My Old Company, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - My Older Brother, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Names, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Napoleon, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - New England Statue, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - A New Look, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Night View, From Above, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Ninety and Eight, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Nineteenth Century Photographs, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - No Sun, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Not Yet The Day, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Now is Always the Miraculous Time, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Oh, Surely, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Old Grief, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Old Handwriting, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - The Old Man at the Window, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - An Old Poem, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Old tom Eakins, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Old Woman at a Poetry Reading, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - On a Train, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - On Sending My Published Verses, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Once in Ephesus, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Once, Sheridan Square, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Order, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Orpheus, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Our Family Doctor, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Our Hands We're Occasionally Touching, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Our Mother, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Our Mother's Ledger, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Observations, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Oedipus, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - O Usual Dream, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - An Occasional Man, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Oh Play That Thing, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Olaf & Sigurd, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Old Billy, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Old Gone Sounds, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - The Old Historian, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Old King, Still King, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - The Old Lady, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - An Old Lunch, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - O God! O Montreal!, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - The Old Black Man and The Cat, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - On The Mall, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Out Walking Late Evening, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Pablo, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Parental, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Pass Christian, Miss, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Passing a Flowerbed, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - The Pedant From Boston, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - The Pennies, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Pharaoh, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - The Piano, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - The Piano Seat Cover, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Phileman to Baucis, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - A Philosophical Discussion, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - The Philosophy Student, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Picking Up Lula, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - The Pine Cone, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Pining, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Piranesi, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Pissarro, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Placement, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Plas Johnson, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - The Poet Upstairs, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Pope John, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - A Poolside Lesson, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Prayer, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Priscilla Gray, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - A Problem in Hermeneutics, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Problems II, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - The process of Building, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - A Proper Reply, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - The Phrophets of Old, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - A Proper Reply, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Protagoras, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Proust, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - The Paratrooper, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Paying Respects In New Jersey, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Peter to John on Judas, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Petersburg, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - The Quality of Mercy, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Questions for Myself, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - The Quotation, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Red Hot Henry Brown, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Reading Finnegan's Wake, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Reading Heidegger, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Reading on a Blowy Night, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Really Reading, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Rearrangements, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - The Recruit, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - The Redemptive Figures, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Rehab, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - The Rejected Lover, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Rembrandt & Hals, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - A Report From Nineveh, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Ripper Redux, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Request to the Old Forerunners, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - A Response, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Rescue at Antietam, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - A Respect for Competence, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - The Reunion, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - The Rite, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Ritter, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - The Road, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - The Rowe, Rambling, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - The Rule, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Ruth and Naomi, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Saint Anthony, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Satan, Second Thoughts, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Second Samuel, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Sentiment, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - The Sentimentalism of Sunsets, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Sentiments to a Lady, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - The Seriousness of Poetry, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Seventeen, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Shakespeare..., Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - She to her Stark Antagonist, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - The Shipmate, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Short Acquaint, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Sidney, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Sidney and Paul, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Sir Isaac, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Sister & Brother, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - A Small Encounter, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Small Pats in the Night, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Small Towns, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Soccer, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Socrates, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Something From Milosz, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - The Spider, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Stories at the Dinner Table, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Song for William James, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - The Son of a Nun, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - The Songwriter, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - A Southern Poet, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Stage Direction, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Starlings, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - The Statement, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Stealthy Days, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - A Street Car Conductor, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - A Student at Alexandria, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - The Studio in August, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Summit Meeting, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - The Story Teller, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Sunrise and Sunset, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Surprise, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - The Technical Lecture, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - A Temporal Consideration, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - That Good Night, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Things that go on between us, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Things of The World, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - This Morning We Are Putting, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Thousands of Poets, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Thomas, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Three Biblical Themes, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Three Poems, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Three Women, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Tin Roof Blues, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Tissot, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - To the Well Known, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Thermopylae, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - The Three Year Old, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - The Second Bowie Poem, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Today's Poetry: Lesson One, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Tom Ramsey, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - The Torturer's Apprentice, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - To Thomas Wolfe, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - The Towers of Rosslyn, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - The Turning Point, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Trees in Winter, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Trimeters, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - A Trip, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Trips, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - The Triumph of L.N. Cole, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Truth in a Parked Car, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Trying To Save Somethings, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - 2020 AD, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Touching the Past, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Twenty Years After, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Two Fish, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - What She Said, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Two Little Savages, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Two Parties, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Two Ways, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Uncle Thompson, About 1900, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - A Useful Phrase, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - The Uses of Journalism, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - The Valedictory, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - To My Wife, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Van Der Leck's Picture, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Vashti, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - The Veterans, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - The Value of Travel, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - The Ventilator Casting, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Veteran Talk, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Vienna's Ring, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - The View, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Virtues, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Using the Past, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - A Visit from Philip Larkin, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - The Visit of the Queen, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Walking the Streets, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Walker, Joint Use, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Waterboy, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - What Happened Once, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - When I Saw Her Last, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - When, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - When the Continents, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Where the Violets Grow, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - While I Listen, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - While Jazz, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - The White House of Uffington, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Whitman and the Astronomers, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - The Wide Bed, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - William White of Deep Creek, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - The Widower, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - The Witch, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - W.M. Christenberry, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - The Winged Chariot, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - A Woman for Hats, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - A Woman From Memphis, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - The Woman of Samaria, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - The Woman on the Elevator, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - A Woman We Know, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Women, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Wondrous News, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - The Words of Bad-Eye Parker, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Words for George Crabbe, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - The Words of My Grandmother, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - The World is a Duck, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - The Writing Lesson, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Yeats, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - The Yew, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - A Young Couple..., Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Young Jazz Lover, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Young Woman Photographer, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Your Return to Golf, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Young Man Away From Home, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - The Zoo, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Zipporah, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Anthology - Red Candle Press, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Art/ Poetry, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Changing World, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Civil War Poems, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Heidegger, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Hermeneutics, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Huxley, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Jazz Poems, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 8)